generic4all.com 2010-02-13

# 

  | 

|  |   
---|---  
  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
  
Categories

    *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     * |  |  More...  
---|---  
  
    *     *     *     * |  More...  
---|---  
  
    *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     * |  More...  
---|---  
  
    *     *     *     *     *     * |  More...  
---|---  

|  |   
  
**Privacy Policy**

**Commitment to Privacy  
** Generic4All understands that your personal information is very important to you. We appreciate your trust in providing any such information to us and are committed to protecting it.  
The personal information we collect includes shipping and billing name and address, email address, phone number and credit card information. This information is used only to complete your order. We do not share your personal information with outside parties for marketing or for any other purpose. We assure you that, in accordance with our Privacy Policy, Generic4All, will not distribute our customer list to third parties.  

**Collected Information & Customer Account Details**  
We recognize our customers’ right to confidentiality and we are committed to protecting our customers’ privacy. We use the information that we collect on our website to provide our customers with a superior shopping experience and also to inform our customers about products, services and promotions whenever we feel it is necessary. We use our customers’ emails only for purchase related purposes. When orders are placed, customers are asked to set up an account with log-in information that includes the customer’s name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date, as well as certain other information. We will not sell our customers’ information to anybody. Customers can always access their account by logging-in to our website and modifying their information at any time.  

**Security**  
Appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures are taken to safeguard and secure the online information that is collected. Customers’ personal information and credit card or debit card data are encrypted using SSL encryption technology before being transmitted over the Internet. SSL technology is used to prevent theft or interception of our customers’ information while being transmitted over the Internet to our servers. Customers’ credit card information is always stored in an encrypted form, in a restricted-access database that is away from our website database. This database is not connected to the Internet, thus is kept safe from external intrusions.  
Generic4All uses secure servers to protect its customers’ personal information, as well as industry-standard SSL encryption to ensure the privacy and security of the transmitted information throughout the checkout process.  
Our system has safeguards in place to protect against credit card fraud. Individuals attempting the fraudulent use credit cards will be reported immediately.  

Brand names appearing on this site are registered trademarks of their respective companies.   
The statements on this website have not been evaluated by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration or other similar international agency. The information on this website is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. Prescription, OTC, nutritional or other products are not offered to diagnose or prescribe medical or psychological conditions, nor claim to prevent, treat, mitigate or cure such conditions, nor to recommend specific products as treatment of disease or to provide diagnosis, care, treatment or rehabilitation of individuals, or apply medical, mental health or human development principles. The information herein is not a substitute for medical advice from your primary care physician. Testimonial results are not typical.
